{
    "id": "7599bd2a97ef426eaf93a9c45cf533dd",
    "title": "Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The winners were two …………………………. from the north.",
            "description": "Woman is the right word. Female is usually an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "women",
                "womans",
                "females"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "db91b76163854df6a670c8f171d481e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He took …………………………….. at this.",
            "description": "These are idiomatic expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "insult",
                "offence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8971cfca074845638eec69011d2b00b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "His brother is a …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drunker",
                "drunkard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6429a200b3ee4e53aacb633e5c5aab71"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are many ……………………………. in the developing countries.",
            "description": "Poor is an adjective. It is used with a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "poors",
                "poor people"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0230e948406e4cc6a02c26afea5eae77"
        },
        {
            "question": "The clock has struck ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nine",
                "nine hours"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e959e2a91a9c4112bccb0fd940e506f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher taught us a new ……………………………….",
            "description": "Poetry is essentially a collection of poems.",
            "answers": [
                "poem",
                "poetry"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e916be7a799429da6b9c9d177088ca9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no ……………………………… on the bus.",
            "description": "This is an idiomatic expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "space",
                "place",
                "room"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "32a051b49c2d48f895d1966f256f039d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He provided ……………………………….. with food.",
            "description": "The poor means all poor people. ",
            "answers": [
                "poors",
                "poor people",
                "the poor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "232fac4bcf344d65aa0dc5521aad9b5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have packed my ………………………………",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "luggage",
                "luggages"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a5f258dd91341a68e6941196b41898c"
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my ……………………………. has left.",
            "description": "Use a plural noun after one of.",
            "answers": [
                "servants",
                "servant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b841d414d0a64d9c8b5a210a94165007"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich man didn’t give the beggar ……………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "nothing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a530df063bc4d58a38630a3e742c569"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very cold in this …………………………….. of the country.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "side",
                "part"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb27ec43cba6400ab4137baf87e99e47"
        }
    ]
}